{"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40092/":{"taskOID":40092,"originalTaskOID":40092,"setID":404,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7165,"questionDisplayText":"Maintenance Frequency","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How often would you like the lawn maintained?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11109,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One time service","answerDisplayText":"One time service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11110,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Twice a week","answerDisplayText":"Twice a week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11111,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Weekly","answerDisplayText":"Weekly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11112,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Biweekly","answerDisplayText":"Biweekly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11113,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Monthly","answerDisplayText":"Monthly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11114,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bimonthly","answerDisplayText":"Bimonthly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7167,"questionDisplayText":"Estimated Size of Lawn","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the estimated size of your lawn?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11127,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft )","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft )","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11128,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11129,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11130,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11131,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7165,"questionDisplayText":"Maintenance Frequency","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How often would you like the lawn maintained?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11109,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One time service","answerDisplayText":"One time service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11110,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Twice a week","answerDisplayText":"Twice a week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11111,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Weekly","answerDisplayText":"Weekly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11112,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Biweekly","answerDisplayText":"Biweekly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11113,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Monthly","answerDisplayText":"Monthly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11114,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bimonthly","answerDisplayText":"Bimonthly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11109,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One time service","answerDisplayText":"One time service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11110,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Twice a week","answerDisplayText":"Twice a week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11111,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Weekly","answerDisplayText":"Weekly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11112,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Biweekly","answerDisplayText":"Biweekly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11113,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Monthly","answerDisplayText":"Monthly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11114,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bimonthly","answerDisplayText":"Bimonthly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7167,"questionDisplayText":"Estimated Size of Lawn","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the estimated size of your lawn?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11127,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft )","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft )","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11128,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11129,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11130,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11131,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11127,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft )","answerDisplayText":"Small (Less than 1,000 sq ft )","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11128,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Medium (1,000 - 3,000 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11129,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Large (3,000 - 10,000 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11130,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Very Large (More than 10,000 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11131,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Lawn Maintenance \u0026 Mowing Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40092/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40092,"taskName":"Lawn Care - Maintain and Mow a Lawn","taskDescription":"Mow Grass and Maintain Landscaping","xmTaskDescriptor":"Lawn Maintenance \u0026 Mowing Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":148,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Landscape Mow grass mowing mowers","textMessagingName":"Maintain Lawn","rolloverLongDesc":"Involves weekly or bi-weekly visits where all maintenance needs are carried out on a regular basis. Some firms will do one-time mowing \u0026 cleanups.","rolloverShortDesc":"Mowing, weeding, trimming \u0026 mulching, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Mow Grass and Maintain Landscaping.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Lawn Maintenance \u0026 Mowing Services","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":48,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Mow \u0026 Maintain a Lawn","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Lawn Care - Maintain and Mow a Lawn","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Lawn Care Project","urlName":"Lawn-Care-Maintain-and-Mow-a-Lawn","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Lawn Maintenance/Mowing Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"Landscape,Mow,grass,mowing,mowers,yard, gardeners,garden,landscaper, Landscaping, Lawn, care, lawncare","emcCategoryOid":-12047,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":404,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}